<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christin &amp; Perry Tea Ceremony</title>
    <link>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Christin &amp; Perry Tea Ceremony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea Ceremony</title>
      <link>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/main_event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/main_event/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive Guide Tuesday, Nov 21, 2017 noon - 3pm Ceremony and reception will be held at The Peninsula Hong Kong Garden Suite  This is different from a traditional American wedding  Ceremony will include a tea ceremony where we serve tea to elders Reception will be held after the ceremony  A east-meets-west style lunch buffet will be served  No dance floor or DJ at the reception Dress code: Garden formal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting There</title>
      <link>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/02_getting_there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/02_getting_there/</guid>
      <description>Fly to Hong Kong International Airport (HKG) The main event starts at Noon, November 21, 2017 Hong Kong local time (GMT +8, 13-16 hour ahead of US mainland time).
For our overseas Guests: Please make sure you depart your home by November 20, 2017 to ensure you would make it to our event.
Transiting via other countries on US passport     Leaving for Hong Kong Leaving for US      Clear custom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lodging</title>
      <link>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/03_lodging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/03_lodging/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Geography Overview: Hong Kong consists of 2 main land masses, which are divided into 3 areas:
* Hong Kong Island
* Kowloon (peninsula off the southern part of New Territory) * New Territory (rest of Hong Kong)
There are also 100s of outlying island，of which the airport is located on one of the largest.
The north side of New Territory connects to mainland China, separated by a river</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication</title>
      <link>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/04_communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/04_communication/</guid>
      <description>Wifi HK airport has free wifi available.
SIM card purchase Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s cell coverage is very good. Pre-paid SIM card is available at HKG airport.
Convenience stores such as 7-11, Circle K, and VanGo offer SIM card and reload voucher.
To use a pre-paid SIM card, you must have a GSM-based unlocked phone. Talk to your neighborhood tech guys for details if you need assistance.
HK airport arrival hall A13 kiosk sells SIM card and a variety of tour packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transit in Hong Kong</title>
      <link>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/05_transit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/05_transit/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s public transportation is very convenient and easy to use. In addition to cash, you can pay for majority of the public transportation with an Octopus card.
Octopus Card The Octopus Card a cash-equivalent, rechargeable RFID card for nearly all public transit.
It is also accepted at convenience store, supermarkets, vending machines, and some restaurants.
There are two main kinds of Octopus Card for Adults. Children (age 3-11) and seniors (age 65+) can enjoy discounts on their travels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour</title>
      <link>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/06_tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samesense.github.io/tea_site/info/06_tour/</guid>
      <description>Group tours We will try to leverage a group discount where applicable, and would notify you if no group discount is available. Please note that we may combine, move or cancel tours depending on signup activities.
*Date would change to maximize people who would like to join
Sign up here
Full Day Tours The following paid full day tours are available. Prices listed are pre-group discount.
   Tour Tour Name Location Price include meal?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>